I'll become strong enough
to eradicate
all the inequality and injustice...
in this world!
You're finished now,
Conqueror Lufas Maphaahl!
Fools.
It's you who are finished!
I'm not done yet.
The Climax skill?!
You took my attacks on purpose?!
Subspace Seal!
Splendidly done, Heroes!
Perhaps you all can defeat him then!
The Devil King, Orm!
Oh damn!
My Lufas really held out to the very end.
Still...
WE CAN JUST CALL THIS THE END OF THE GAME, YEAH?
- It was a big hit.
I have no regrets.
Hmm?
Alovenus, Goddess of all Creation?
That's the goddess who created
the world of Exgate in this setting, right?
Does that mean this is an official
message from the company?
Lufas had become a major boss on par
with the Devil King at this point.
I guess the company had to do something
about what happened, right?
I don't know what kind of role
you have planned,
WILL YOU ACCEPT?
- but I'll take it on!
They've appeared! The Hero!
- Then the summoning worked?!
- What is this?
- W-What?
- What's going on?
That woman is-!
- W-We didn't get the Hero...
- Where am I?
- We've broken the seal on her!
- Some prank?
Boobs?!They're heavy!
H-Huh?!
And there's something... something on my back?
Have I...
become Lufas?!
No, no! No way!
"Watching a cute girl is more
motivating than some guy!"
was the stupid reason I spent several hours
agonizing over character creation!
I can't watch her if I am her!
A dream?!
Or have I been sucked into the game?!
Impossible. That only happens in manga!
For now I need information!
U-Umm, do you have a moment?
Well, well, we have yet to grasp
what's going on here,
would you care to explain it to us?
No! That's not what I meant!
- I just have a few questions—
- What's the matter, children of men?
Raise your heads.
Is that the standard posture
you take amongst yourselves?
If so, then we apologize for our ignorance.
That's so wrong!
This just sounds like an indirect insult!
And what's wrong with the way I'm talking?!
It's what I used when I
role-played Lufas in the game!
Then there's this pressure too!
Right! Her racial skill, Pressure!
That's probably active right now!
Calm down, my intimidation!
Calm down, calm down!
We have been thoughtless.
Of course you would find it
challenging to talk like this.
Stop the skill!
Take it easy, Pressure!
Please stop!
Please!
The air's...
back to normal?
T-There's no doubt!
We've truly resurrected the Conqueror!
You there, elf.
You seem to know of us.
So we shall have you explain
the state of affairs.
Do not be frightened.
Simply tell us everything.
...and there you have it.
I see.
Two hundred years have passed
since we were sealed.
The Devil King lives still.
Thus, to defeat him, you tried
using Exgate to summon a Hero,
and we appeared instead.
Y-Yes.
Does that mean I'm really in the game?
I'm really here two hundred years
after the Mizgarz I knew?
I'm surprised to see them
using the Exgate spell.
It was just a name before.
The name Exgate Online originated from it
and it was a cornerstone of the game.
No, I can't go into the lore now, I have to
do something about this situation first!
They're incredibly frightened,
I should leave soon.
Ahem.
To think the Devil King is still alive
after all this time.
But fear not.
We have no intention of
doing anything with this world.
We may have been defeated,
but we were satisfied with that battle.
Right now we are not the Conqueror, Lufas,
but a mere young girl whose hopes were dashed.
W-Where are you going?
I want to see the world and
appreciate it as it is.
Therefore, you may forget about us and conduct
another Hero Summoning or whatever pleases you.
We shall meet again, if the chance arises.
And somehow, I understand
how to move my wings!
To be honest,
I've been excited by this situation.
Because I get to see my beloved
world of Exgate Online,
and I get to walk through it as Lufas!
A WILD LAST BOSS APPEARS!
As a gamer, what could
be more fun than this?!
As for how to get back to my world...
Well, I'll figure that out later!
Hmm?
That's...
I see! So it's still around?
I know where I'm headed next!
Exgate Online.
An online fantasy game
about swords and sorcery,
set in the parallel world of Mizgarz.
The draw of the game was its "War" system.
WAR SYSTEM
- Different nations engaged in PvP combat.
The winners conquered the losing nation.
Another one of its draws
was its "Novel" system.
It was a system that adapted
players' in-game actions
into a story that was published
as its official history.
I made Lufas the strongest character
I possibly could.
I raised her level, spent money on items, and
maintained my position as the game's top player.
And then...
I finally managed to unify Mizgarz for
the first time in the game's history,
and that was given the grand
treatment by the Novel system.
She even became a semi-official
character in the game.
However, an era with a single, powerful
ruler doesn't make for a very fun game.
So I negotiated with the
other high-level players
to split our forces into the
Conqueror's Army led by Lufas
and the Army of Light led by the "Heroes,"
and we conducted a War.
We held the greatest battle
in the history of the game,
completely ignoring the official final boss!
Then I—err, Lufas, rather—lost,
and got sealed away in subspace.
Never thought I'd actually
get to come here to my—
THE SKY TOWER OF MAPHAAHL
- No, to our base, the Sky Tower of Maphaahl.
Hmm?
Of course it's seen decline.
Though the spirit remains.
What an odd feeling.
It's our first time actually seeing it,
but it feels nostalgic.
Right. Back then I had my friends with me.
We'd chat about how we were
going to expand our forces,
down liquor like fools,
and revel in our merriment.
What was that memory just now?
Mistress Lufas!
It's really you, Mistress Lufas Maphaahl!
It's been so long!
I've been waiting for your return
for the past two hundred years!
- And you...
- Yes!
...would be?
Gah!
Only those we have permitted to enter
should be able to enter this tower.
H-Have you forgotten me?
It's me! Your loyal advisor, Dina!
Advisor? We never...
When I created our base, I placed a
young NPC here as part of the backdrop.
I think I remember giving her the
odd background of "Lufas's Advisor."
So a background NPC gained self-awareness
and waited for me?
Is this... not the game world?
Forgive us, Dina.
Something must be wrong with us
to forget about one as loyal as you.
You have served us well.
Good work protecting this
tower during our absence.
Y-You honor me with your words!
...and so, we were summoned from
subspace and able to return.
So that's how.
Those humans who summoned you
must have been quite shocked.
Shocked would be putting it mildly.
I don't blame them.
The nation to the west?
That would be Laevateinn.
They've been preparing the
Hero Summoning for a while now.
Dina. Could you inform us of what
has occurred since we departed?
Yes!
First of all, the loathsome
Heroes that defeated you...
they later became known as the Seven Heroes,
and they each founded their own nation.
Four of them have already passed from old age,
and the three with longer
lifespans are still alive.
Hmm, the Seven Heroes?
I wonder if they're actually
other players like me?
The Devil King remains alive and well.
Though that's because the Devil King
crushed the Seven Heroes.
Sheesh, talk about disappointing and useless.
What else?
The Twelve Heavenly Stars are still around.
Oh?
The Twelve Heavenly Stars' proper name was
the Conquering Twelve Heavenly Stars.
They were what you would call
companion monster NPCs.
I was lucky to recruit several rare
monsters that were difficult to obtain,
and I granted the title of
Twelve Heavenly Stars
to the ones that were especially powerful.
There was a time when I
thought that a major boss
should have something like the classic
"four elite generals" serving them.
How are they all faring?
I know the whereabouts of six.
Two of them joined the Devil King's army to
seek vengeance on the humans who defeated you.
They joined the Devil King?
Even though our own shame invited that,
that was a terribly disgraceful thing to do.
It seems we need to give
them a good reaming out.
Still, this is good.
Now we have a goal.
We were hoping to see the current state
of the world for ourselves as well.
I need to verify if the three
Heroes are also players like me.
Not to mention...
Dina.
We're now setting out on a journey
to gather the Twelve Heavenly Stars.
It's our responsibility to stop those
who would act foolishly.
Yes!
The one closest to our
current location is here:
Svel.
This is where one of the Seven Heroes,
Megrez, has taken up residence,
and one of the Twelve Heavenly Stars,
Aries the Ram,
is located at the base of the nearby volcano.
Aries has been repeatedly trying to invade Svel.
Then it seems...
- we have our destination.
- Wait!
- Please wait, Mistress Lufas!
- What is it?
Are you planning to go there
without making any preparations?
Do you have any money on you?
Do you not have any?
After waiting for you for so long,
I've become penniless!
Then we simply must earn the funds.
Right.
However, I must inform you that
will be incredibly difficult.
Mistress Lufas, your face is too well-known now.
Over two hundred years have passed.
- There shouldn't be any who remember—
- Naive! That's naive!
Long-lived races like the elves still have
fresh memories of you, Mistress Lufas!
Especially those wings!
Those black wings stand out in a bad way!
They're considered abhorrent
among the heaven-winged!
But black is common, right?
If anything, it's plain and dull?
It's not. Common. At all!
Fine, fine. Stop shouting.
Then what do you suggest we do?
There's just one way to earn money.
This job doesn't care about
your background or identity!
Hmm?
Ah, risking your life for money.
In other words,
adventuring.
That's right!
Let's go accept quests as adventurers
and earn their rewards!
TRADE CITY
OF YDALIR
Dina, it's difficult to walk like this.
Please bear with it.
You're famous, after all.
You don't want to draw
unwanted attention, right?
We think we're drawing a
different kind of attention.
H-Hello.
This sense of being in a den of lowlifes...
it's nostalgic.
That reminds me, you were an adventurer
before you founded your nation, weren't you?
Yes.
"Nostalgic"?
Hmm? Is something the matter?
Think nothing of it.
I'm overthinking it.
- What about this one?
- Which one?
Twelve hundred el just for
finding a dozen cats!
That's a bargain!
That is an exceptional reward,
but finding things is not our forte.
That's what beastfolk are talented in.
I see. Hmm...
How about this one?!
Exterminating orcs?
ORCS (PORK BOWLS)
- Orcs. Also called "pork bowls".
- When you defeated one in the game,
there was a 3% chance they would drop
"Orc Meat," an item that raised your Max HP.
ORCS (PORK BOWLS)
- A solid choice for farming.
Hmm. The reward is 1500 el?
That will suffice.
AISLE VILLAGE
They've wreaked havoc on our village,
kidnapped our women,
and killed our younger men.
We can't take it anymore.
Please deliver judgment to those
loathsome pigs any way you can!
Yes! Those orcs will be thoroughly
crushed, along with their den!
By this woman!
Please save our village.
Please.
Of course.
Consider the matter settled.
Every time I see them, they're just so hideous.
I bet even Goddess Alovenus surely laments
creating such a revolting failure!
You have quite the sharp tongue.
Those of the cloth teach
that the goddess is merciful
and loves all equally.
That's a blatant lie!
The goddess is quite a picky woman!
Oh? Is that so?
Now, please wipe those orcs out quickly!
Mistress Lufas!
As you wish.
Let's eliminate them quickly.
That's right. Maybe I'm still
able to check my stats?
LUFAS MAPHAAHL
- Good. I'm at max level.
- Everything seems consistent with the game.
So then it's on me.
Can I truly bring myself to kill monsters?
Alchemize.
Whoa!
Execute.
Ugh! Gross!
It's odd.
My mind isn't disturbed by this.
Mistress Lufas!
Slow.
They're too slow.
Why are they moving like
they aren't even trying?
Are these things screwing around?
There's no need to generate swords.
So frail.
Far too frail.
Hey,
did you not see what we just did?
Hmm.
I understand.
There's an overwhelming gap between the
flow of time for myself and the orcs.
They aren't frail or slow.
I'm simply too strong and fast.
This isn't even combat.
It's not even playing around.
This is...
just simple slaughter.
EPISODE 1
A WILD LAST BOSS APPEARS!